<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ZhiShui</string>
    <string name="content1">The trouble is that innovation involves trying to hit a moving target. Environments constantly shift and pose new threats – new technologies appear, new markets emerge, the regulatory framework changes – and unless organizations have the capacity to innovate their approaches to innovation they may not survive in the long term. History is clear about this – very few organizations are long-term survivors and those which have managed to stick around for over 100 years have made some major changes to what they do and how they do it (Francis et al., 2003). Sometimes the changes are pretty dramatic, challenging the roots of where the company began and overturning a lot in the process. TUI, for example, is the largest European travel and tourism services company, owning (amongst others) Thomson Holidays, Britannia Airways, and Lunn Poly travel agents. Its origins, however, go back to 1917 where it began as the Prussian state-owned lead mining and smelting company! Nokia’s key role as a leader in mobile telephony hides its origins as a diverse timber products conglomerate with interests as wide as rubber boots and toilet paper!</string>
    <string name="angry1">How you behave when you’re angry depends on
        how well you’re able to identify and cope with your feelings,
        and how you’ve learned to express them.Not everyone expresses
        anger in the same way. For example, some
        unhelpful ways you may have learned to express anger include:\n
    • Outward aggression and violence – such as shouting, swearing,
        slamming doors, hitting or throwing things and being physically
        violent or verbally abusive and threatening towards others.\n
    • Inward aggression – such as telling yourself that you hate
        yourself, denying yourself your basic needs (like food, or things that
        might make you happy), cutting yourself off from the world and
        self-harming.\n
    • Non-violent or passive aggression – such as ignoring people or
        refusing to speak to them, refusing to do tasks, or deliberately doing
        things poorly, late or at the last possible minute, and being sarcastic
        or sulky while not saying anything explicitly aggressive or angry.\n
        If you find you express your anger through outward aggression and
        violence, this can be extremely frightening and damaging for people
        around you – especially children. And it can have serious consequences: it
        could lose you your job or get you into trouble with the law. In this case
        it’s very important to seek treatment and support.
        But even if you’re never outwardly violent or aggressive towards others,
        and never even raise your voice, you might still recognise some of these
        angry behaviours and feel that they’re a problem for you.</string>
    <string name="angry2">It can be frightening when your anger overwhelms you. But there are ways you can learn to stay in control of your anger when you find yourself in difficult situations. You can:\n
    • look out for warning signs. Anger can cause a rush of adrenaline through your body, so before you recognise the emotion you’re feeling you might notice: your heart is beating faster; your breathing is
        quicker; your body is becoming tense; your feet are tapping; you’re clenching your jaw or fists. Recognising these signs gives you the chance to think about how you want to react to a situation
        before doing anything. This can be difficult in the heat of the moment, but the earlier you notice how you’re feeling, the easier it can be to choose how to manage your anger.\n
    • buy yourself time to think. Sometimes when we’re feeling angry, we just need to walk away from the
        situation for a while. This can give you time to work out what you’re
        thinking about the situation, decide how you want to react to it and feel
        more in control. Some ways you can buy yourself time to think are: Counting to 10 before you react;
        Going for a short walk – even if it’s just around your local area;
        Talking to a trusted friend who’s not connected to the situation.
        Expressing your thoughts out loud can help you understand why
        you’re angry and help calm you down.\n
    • try some calming techniques. There are many ways to calm down and let go of angry feelings,
        depending on what suits you and what’s convenient at the time you are
        angry.Breathe slowly – try to breathe out for longer than you breathe in
        and focus on each breath as you take it. Relax your body – if you can feel your body getting tense, try
        focusing on each part of your body in turn to tense and then relax
        your muscles. Use up some of your energy safely – this can help relieve some
        of your angry feelings in a way that doesn’t hurt yourself or others.
        For example, you could try: tearing up a newspaper, hitting a pillow, smashing ice cubes in a sink.
         Do something to distract yourself. Anything that completely
        changes your situation, thoughts or patterns can help stop your
        anger escalating. For example, you could try:putting on upbeat music and dancing,
        doing some colouring, taking a cold shower. </string>
    <string name="angry3">If you think about how to manage your anger when you’re feeling calmer,
    you can avoid feeling overwhelmed by it in the heat of the moment. You
    can:\n
    • learn your triggers. Understanding what sort of situations trigger your anger means you can
        develop strategies to cope and think about how to react before the
        situation happens. You might find it helpful to keep a diary or make notes
        about the times you have felt angry. You could record: What were the circumstances?
        Did someone say or do something to trigger your anger? How did you feel?
        How did you behave? How did you feel afterwards?
        If you do this for a while, you might start to see patterns emerging. You
        could do this yourself using a free online mood diary, such as Mood Panda, or you could find a professional therapist to help you.\n

    • examine your thought patterns. If you’re feeling upset or angry, you might find yourself automatically
        thinking or saying things like: “This is all their fault.”; “They never listen.”; “This always happens to me.”; “Other people should behave better.”.
        But often there are lots of different ways we could interpret a situation. It
        can make you feel worse if you think in terms of ‘always’, ‘never’ and
        ‘should’, because in reality things are rarely so black and white. Making an
        effort to replace these words with softer terms like ‘sometimes’ or ‘could’
        when thinking about your situation might help you to break up negative
        thought patterns, reflect more calmly on your situation and find new ways
        through conflicts.
        You can use online tools like Player 2 or MoodGym to help you examine
        how you’re thinking and feeling, and help you think about other ways you
        could view a situation. \n

    • develop your communication skills. Being excessively angry and aggressive can get in the way of
        communicating your feelings effectively. People may focus on your anger,
        and find it hard to listen to what you’re saying. On the other hand, if you
        are able to express your anger by talking in an assertive, respectful way
        about what has made you angry, then you’re more likely to be understood
        by others. Learning to be assertive might not feel easy to start with, but here are
        some things to try: 1) Think about the outcome you want to achieve. What’s making
        you angry, and what do you want to change? Is it enough just to
        explain what you are angry about? 2) Be specific. For example, you could open your statement with, “I
        feel angry with you because…” Using the phrase ‘I feel’ avoids
        blaming anyone and the other person is less likely to feel attacked. 3) Really listen to the other person’s response and try to
        understand their point of view. 4) Be prepared for the conversation to go wrong and try to spot
        when this is happening. If you feel yourself getting angry, you might
        want to come back to the conversation another time.\n

    • look at your lifestyle. Looking after your well-being more generally could help you feel calmer
        and more in control when things happen that make you feel angry. You
        might want to: Avoid drugs and alcohol; Be more active; Get good sleep; Learn to deal with pressure; Develop your emotional resilience.</string>

    <string name="depression1">
    • Get good sleep. For lots of people who experience depression,
        sleeping too little or too much can be a daily problem. Getting good
        sleep can help to improve your mood and increase your energy
        levels. See Mind’s booklet How to cope with sleep problems for
        more information.\n
    • Eat well. Eating a balanced and nutritious diet can help you feel
        well, think clearly and increase your energy levels. See Mind’s
        booklet Exploring food and mood for more tips.\n
    • Keep active. Many people find exercise a challenge but gentle
        activities like yoga, swimming or walking can be a big boost to your
        mood. See Mind’s booklet How to improve your well-being through
        physical activity and sport for more information.\n
    • Look after your hygiene. When you’re experiencing depression,
        it’s easy for hygiene to not feel like a priority. But small things, like
        taking a shower and getting fully dressed whether or not you’re
        going out of the house, can make a big difference to how you feel. \n
    • Avoid drugs and alcohol. While you might want to use drugs or
        alcohol to cope with any difficult feelings, in the long run they can
        make you feel a lot worse. See Mind’s online booklet Understanding
        the mental health effects of street drugs for more information.</string>
    <string name="depression2">
    • Work out what makes you happy. Try making a list of activities,
        people and places that make you happy or feel good. Then make a
        list of what you do every day. It probably won’t be possible to
        include all the things that make you happy but try to find ways to
        bring those things into your daily routine.
    • Treat yourself. When you’re feeling down, it can be hard to feel
        good about yourself. Try to do at least one positive thing for yourself
        every day. This could be taking the time for a long bath, spending
        time with a pet or reading your favourite book. See Mind’s booklet
        Exploring relaxation for some ideas of things to do.
    • Create a resilience toolkit. This could be a list of activities you
        know improve your mood, or you could fill an actual box with things
        to do to cheer yourself up. Try including your favourite book or film,
        a notebook and pen to write down your thoughts or notes of
        encouragement to yourself. It might feel difficult or a bit silly to put
        it all together but it can be a really useful tool if you’re feeling too
        low to come up with ideas later on.
    • Be kind to yourself. None of us achieve all our goals. Don’t beat
        yourself up if you don’t do something you planned to, or find
        yourself feeling worse again. Try to treat yourself as you would treat
        a friend, and be kind to yourself. </string>
    <string name="depression3">
    • Join a group. This could be anything from a community project or
        a sports team to a hobby group. The important thing is to find an
        activity you enjoy, or perhaps something you’ve always wanted to
        try, to help you feel motivated.\n
    • Try new things. Trying something new, like starting a new hobby,
        learning something new or even trying new food, can help boost
        your mood and break unhelpful patterns of thinking and behaviour.\n
    • Try volunteering. Volunteering (or just offering to help someone
        out) can make you feel better about yourself and less alone.
        Volunteering England, Volunteering Wales and Do-It can help match
        you with a volunteering opportunity in your area.\n
    • Set realistic goals. Try to set yourself achievable goals, like
        getting dressed every day or cooking yourself a meal. Achieving
        your goals can help you feel good and boost your self-confidence,
        and help you move on to bigger ones. </string>
    <string name="depression4">
    • Keep a mood diary. This can help you keep track of any changes
        in your mood, and you might find that you have more good days
        than you think. It can also help you notice if any activities, places or
        people make you feel better or worse.\n
    • Challenge your thinking. Students Against Depression has lots of
        information and activity sheets to try to help you challenge negative
        thinking.\n
    • Try self-help. If your depression is mild, you might find free online
        cognitive behavioural therapy (CBT) courses like MoodGYM (web:
        moodgym.anu.edu.au) can help you tackle some of your negative
        thinking and avoid your depression growing worse.\n
    • Contact a helpline. If you’re struggling with difficult feelings, and
        you can’t talk to someone you know, there are many helplines you
        can contact. These are not professional counselling services but the
        people you speak to are trained to listen and could help you feel
        more able to cope with your low mood. </string>
    <string name="depression5">
    • Keep in touch. If you don’t feel up to seeing people in person, or
        talking, send a text or email to keep in touch with friends and
        family.\n
    • Keep talking. It might feel hard to start talking to your friends and
        family about what you’re feeling, but many people find that just
        sharing their experiences can help them feel better.\n
    • Join a peer support group. Going to a peer support group is a
        great way to share tips and meet other people who are going
        through similar things. Organisations like Depression Alliance and
        Depression UK offer support for anyone experiencing depression,
        while Students Against Depression offers student-specific support.\n
    • Use online support. Online support can be a useful way to build a
        support network when you cannot, or don’t feel able to, do things in
        person. Online forums like Elefriends and Big White Wall are
        specifically for anyone struggling with their mental health.</string>

    <string name="stress1">Even though there are likely to be some things happening in your life
that you can not control, there are still lots of practical things you can do to
manage the amount of pressure you are under day to day.\n
• Identify your triggers.\n
Working out what triggers stress for you can help you anticipate problems
and think of ways to solve them. Even if you can not avoid these situations,
being prepared can help. Take some time to reflect on events and feelings
that could be contributing to your stress (you might want to do this with a
friend or family member).
You could consider: issues that come up regularly, and that you worry about, for example
paying a bill or attending an appointment; one-off events that are on your mind a lot, such as moving house or
taking an exam; ongoing stressful events, like being a carer or having problems at work.
You might be surprised to find out just how much you are coping with at
once. Remember that not having enough work, activities or change in your
life can be just as stressful a situation as having too much to deal with.\n
• Organise your time.\n
Making some adjustments to the way you organise your time could help
you feel more in control of any tasks you are facing, and more able to
handle pressure. Identify your best time of day, and do the important tasks that need
the most energy and concentration at that time. For example, you
might be a morning person or an evening person.\n
• Make a list of things you have to do.\n Arrange them in order of
importance, and try to focus on the most urgent first. If your tasks are
work related, ask a manager or colleague to help you prioritise. You
may be able to push back some tasks until you are feeling less stressed. Vary your activities. Balance interesting tasks with more mundane ones,
and stressful tasks with those you find easier or can do more calmly.
Try not to do too much at once. If you take on too much, you might
find it harder to do any individual task well. This can make you feel
like you have even more pressure on you.
Take breaks and take things slowly. It might be difficult to do this
when you are stressed, but it can make you more productive.\n
• Address some of the causes of stress.\n
Although there will probably lots of things in your life that you can not do
anything about, there might still be some practical ways you could to
resolve or improve some of the issues that are putting pressure on you.
You might find it helpful to read some of our other booklets on issues
around mental health, family and personal life, work life, student life,
finances, housing and legal rights.\n
• Accept the things you can not change.\n
It\'s not easy, but accepting that there are some things happening to you
that you probably can\'t do anything about will help you focus your time
and energy more productively.</string>
    <string name="stress2">
Taking steps to look after your well-being can help you deal with pressure,
and reduce the impact that stress has on your life. This is sometimes
called developing emotional resilience – the ability to adapt and bounce
back when something difficult happens in your life.\n
• Make some lifestyle changes\n
There are some general changes that you can make to your lifestyle
that could help you feel more able to cope with pressure and stressful
situations. You can: practice being straightforward and assertive in communicating with
others; use relaxation techniques; develop your interests and hobbies; make time for your friends; find balance in your life.\n
• Look after your physical health\n
Taking steps to look after your physical health can help you manage stress
and lessen the impact on your overall mental health. For example: get good sleep;
be more physically active; eat healthily.\n
• Give yourself a break\n
Learning to be kinder to yourself in general can help you control the
amount of pressure you feel in different situations, which can help you
feel less stressed. Reward yourself for achievements – even small things like finishing
a piece of work or making a decision. You could take a walk, read a
book, treat yourself to food you enjoy, or simply tell yourself "well done". Get a change of scenery. You might want to go outside, go to a friend’s
house or go to a café for a break – even if it is just for a short time.
 Take a break or holiday. Time away from your normal routine can
help you relax and feel refreshed. Even spending a day in a different
place can help you feel more able to face stress.
 Resolve conflicts, if you can. Although this can sometimes be hard,
speaking to a manager, colleague or family member about problems in
your relationship with them can help you find ways to move forward.
 Forgive yourself when you make a mistake, or don\'t achieve
something you hoped for. Try to remember that nobody is perfect, and
putting extra pressure on yourself doesn\'t help.</string>
    <string name="stress3">Stress isn\'t a medical diagnosis, so there\'s no specific treatment for it.
However, if you\'re finding it very hard to cope with things going on in
your life and are experiencing lots of signs of stress, there are treatments
available that could help.\n
• Talking treatments\n
Talking with a trained professional can help you learn to deal with stress
and become more aware of your own thoughts and feelings.\n
• Ecotherapy\n
Ecotherapy is a way of improving your well-being and self-esteem by
spending time in nature. This can include physical exercise in green
spaces or taking part in a gardening or conservation project.\n
• Complementary and alternative therapies\n
You may find certain alternative therapies help you manage feelings of
stress. These might include acupuncture, aromatherapy, massage or
Traditional Chinese Medicine. \n</string>

    <string name="relax1">Lie down or sit with your back straight and your feet on the floor.\n
Close your eyes or focus on a spot in the distance.\n
Start by clenching your toes as much as you can for a few seconds then releasing them. Notice the difference between the two feelings.\n
Match this to your breathing.\n
Tense your muscles as you take
a deep breath in, and relax as you breathe out.\n
Move up your body, clenching and relaxing each muscle. Take time to notice any parts of your body that
feel tense, tight or tired.\n
You can repeat if you still feel tense.\n
Take a moment to relax, then slowly and gently begin to move. When you feel ready, you can stand up slowly.</string>
    <string name="relax2">Make sure you are sitting comfortably with your feet firmly on the floor, your back straight and your shoulders relaxed.\n
Take your paper and crayon, and draw a circle that fills most of the page – don’t worry if it’s a bit wonky!\n
Now keep drawing. You could keep going over the circle, or fill it with a pattern, but try not to let your crayon leave the page. Don’t worry about creating a finished picture, just keep going.\n
Take time to focus on what you’re drawing.\n
Focusing on these sensations can help you quieten your mind,
like meditation.\n
Once you have done this for a few minutes, try using a different colour or pattern.</string>
    <string name="relax3">Music can relax you, connect you to
your emotions and distract you from worrying thoughts.\n
    Listen to your favourite songs. Turn up the volume and dance or sing along, or put your headphones on and close your eyes.\n
Really listen to the music. Can you pick out different instruments? Can you hear a drum beat or a certain rhythm? Focus on the music, and let other thoughts fade away.</string>

    <string name="panic1">A panic attack is an exaggeration of your body’s normal response to fear,
stress or excitement. It is the rapid build-up of overwhelming physical
sensations, such as: a pounding heartbeat; feeling faint; sweating; nausea (feeling sick); chest pains; feeling unable to breathe; shaky limbs, or feeling like your legs are turning to jelly
; feeling like you’re not connected to your body.</string>
    <string name="panic2">It’s different for different people. You might have a good understanding
about situations or places that are likely to trigger an attack for you, or you
might feel that your attacks come without warning and happen at random. \n
Panic attacks can also come in the night while you’re asleep, and wake
you up. This can happen if your brain is very alert (due to anxiety), and
interprets small changes in your body as a sign of danger.\n
Experiencing a panic attack during the night can be particularly
frightening, as you may feel confused about what’s happening, and are
helpless to do anything to spot it coming.</string>
    <string name="panic3">Having a panic attack can be a truly terrifying experience, but there are
things you can do:\n
• Try shifting your focus\n
You may find it helpful to shift your focus or distract yourself from the
anxiety you are feeling. Look at a flower, a picture or something that you
find interesting or comforting. Really notice the details, the colours and
any smells or sounds.\n
• Try a breathing exercise\n
You may find a breathing exercise helps you to manage anxiety and feel
calmer.
Gently breathe in through your nose and out through your mouth, keeping
the pace slow and regular. Slowly tense then relax all the muscles in your
body, starting at your toes and working up to your head. Afterwards just
take some time to be still and focus on how your body feels. </string>
</resources>
